[
	{ "question": "morning", "answer": "あさ" },
	{ "question": "breakfast", "answer": "あさごはん" },
	{ "question": "tomorrow", "answer": "あした" },
	{ "question": "after", "answer": "あと" },
	{ "question": "take(a shower)", "answer": "あびます" },
	{ "question": "wash", "answer": "あらいます" },
	{ "question": "go", "answer": "いきます" },
	{ "question": "one day", "answer": "いちにち" },
	{ "question": "sea", "answer": "うみ" },
	{ "question": "exercise", "answer": "うんどう" },
	{ "question": "get up", "answer": "おきます" },
	{ "question": "sushi", "answer": "おすし" },
	{ "question": "bath", "answer": "おふろ" },
	{ "question": "end", "answer": "おわります" },
	{ "question": "music", "answer": "おんがく" },
	{ "question": "company", "answer": "かいしゃ" },
	{ "question": "buy", "answer": "かいます" },
	{ "question": "return/go back", "answer": "かえります" },
	{ "question": "take(~10 minutes)", "answer": "かかります" },
	{ "question": "tuesday", "answer": "かようび" },
	{ "question": "listen(~to music)", "answer": "ききます" },
	{ "question": "today", "answer": "きょう" },
	{ "question": "friday", "answer": "きんようび" },
	{ "question": "classical music", "answer": "クラシック" },
	{ "question": "come", "answer": "きます" },
	{ "question": "cake", "answer": "ケーキ" },
	{ "question": "monday", "answer": "げつようび" },
	{ "question": "afternoon", "answer": "ごご" },
	{ "question": "in the morning", "answer": "ごぜんちゅう" },
	{ "question": "meal/rice", "answer": "ごはん" },
	{ "question": "about/around", "answer": "ごろ" },
	{ "question": "tonight", "answer": "こんばん" },
	{ "question": "sandwich", "answer": "サンドイッチ" },
	{ "question": "o'clock", "answer": "じ" },
	{ "question": "hour", "answer": "じかん" },
	{ "question": "newspaper", "answer": "しんぶん" },
	{ "question": "wednesday", "answer": "すいようび" },
	{ "question": "skirt", "answer": "スカート" },
	{ "question": "do", "answer": "します" },
	{ "question": "washing machine", "answer": "せんたくき" },
	{ "question": "cleaning/sweeping", "answer": "そうじ" },
	{ "question": "and", "answer": "そして" },
	{ "question": "and then", "answer": "それから" },
	{ "question": "university", "answer": "だいがく" },
	{ "question": "eat", "answer": "たべます" },
	{ "question": "someone", "answer": "だれか" },
	{ "question": "near", "answer": "ちかい" },
	{ "question": "department store", "answer": "デパート" },
	{ "question": "leave/go out", "answer": "でます" },
	{ "question": "subway", "answer": "でんしゃ" },
	{ "question": "how long/how much", "answer": "どのくらい" },
	{ "question": "saturday", "answer": "どようび" },
	{ "question": "summer vacation", "answer": "なつやすみ" },
	{ "question": "something", "answer": "なにか" },
	{ "question": "what day", "answer": "なにょうび" },
	{ "question": "sunday", "answer": "にちようび" },
	{ "question": "japanese language institute", "answer": "にほんごがっこう" },
	{ "question": "go to bed/sleep/lie down", "answer": "ねます" },
	{ "question": "drink", "answer": "のみます" },
	{ "question": "get on/ride", "answer": "のります" },
	{ "question": "tooth/teeth", "answer": "は" },
	{ "question": "party", "answer": "パーティー" },
	{ "question": "enter/take(a bath)", "answer": "はいります" },
	{ "question": "box", "answer": "はこ" },
	{ "question": "begin/start", "answer": "はじまります" },
	{ "question": "bus", "answer": "バス" },
	{ "question": "early", "answer": "はやい" },
	{ "question": "half(past time)", "answer": "はん" },
	{ "question": "(one hour and)half", "answer": "はん" },
	{ "question": "bread", "answer": "パン" },
	{ "question": "dinner/evening meal", "answer": "ばんごはん" },
	{ "question": "second", "answer": "びょう" },
	{ "question": "lunch", "answer": "ひるごはん" },
	{ "question": "lunch break", "answer": "ひるやすみ" },
	{ "question": "review", "answer": "ふくしゅう" },
	{ "question": "winter vacation", "answer": "ふゆやすみ" },
	{ "question": "minute", "answer": "ふん" },
	{ "question": "hall", "answer": "ホール" },
	{ "question": "every morning", "answer": "まいあさ" },
	{ "question": "every day", "answer": "まいにち" },
	{ "question": "every night", "answer": "まいばん" },
	{ "question": "before(a meal)", "answer": "まえ" },
	{ "question": "(five minutes) before (10)", "answer": "まえ" },
	{ "question": "brush/polish", "answer": "みがきます" },
	{ "question": "see/watch", "answer": "みます" },
	{ "question": "thursday", "answer": "もくようび" },
	{ "question": "off day/holiday", "answer": "やすみのひ" },
	{ "question": "preparation for lessons", "answer": "よしゅう" },
	{ "question": "read", "answer": "よみます" },
	{ "question": "night", "answer": "よる" },
	{ "question": "student studying abroad", "answer": "りゅうがくせい" }
]
